{"sid": "C5S4R9TLPDY8_main", "calc_equals_delay": 5, "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 9, "start_time": 334759, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 334760, "question": "88+73+24+53", "correct_answer": 238, "events": [["submit", 354114]], "time_left_end": "281", "answered_time": 354114, "user_answer": "238", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "281", "question_time_start": 354114, "question": "7+17+17", "correct_answer": 41, "events": [["submit", 357802]], "time_left_end": "277", "answered_time": 357801, "user_answer": "51", "user_correct": "False", "score": "0"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "277", "question_time_start": 357802, "question": "24+179", "correct_answer": 203, "events": [["submit", 365069]], "time_left_end": "270", "answered_time": 365069, "user_answer": "203", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "270", "question_time_start": 365069, "question": "3+37+76", "correct_answer": 116, "events": [["submit", 368421]], "time_left_end": "267", "answered_time": 368421, "user_answer": "116", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "267", "question_time_start": 368421, "question": "33+86+14+77", "correct_answer": 210, "events": [["submit", 374556]], "time_left_end": "261", "answered_time": 374556, "user_answer": "210", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "261", "question_time_start": 374557, "question": "47+69+759", "correct_answer": 875, "events": [["submit", 394365]], "time_left_end": "241", "answered_time": 394365, "user_answer": "887", "user_correct": "False", "score": "2"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "241", "question_time_start": 394365, "question": "68+818", "correct_answer": 886, "events": [["submit", 403489]], "time_left_end": "232", "answered_time": 403489, "user_answer": "896", "user_correct": "False", "score": "1"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "232", "question_time_start": 403490, "question": "98+744", "correct_answer": 842, "events": [["submit", 408059]], "time_left_end": "227", "answered_time": 408059, "user_answer": "842", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "227", "question_time_start": 408060, "question": "9+3+7+44", "correct_answer": 63, "events": [["submit", 413372]], "time_left_end": "222", "answered_time": 413372, "user_answer": "63", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "222", "question_time_start": 413373, "question": "9+9+6+84", "correct_answer": 108, "events": [["submit", 417943]], "time_left_end": "217", "answered_time": 417943, "user_answer": "108", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 9, "start_time": 417944, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "217", "question_time_start": 417944, "question": "16+96+23+18", "correct_answer": 153, "events": [["submit", 434350]], "time_left_end": "201", "answered_time": 434350, "user_answer": "153", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "201", "question_time_start": 434350, "question": "4+17+86", "correct_answer": 107, "events": [["submit", 437668]], "time_left_end": "198", "answered_time": 437668, "user_answer": "107", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "198", "question_time_start": 437668, "question": "28+66+138", "correct_answer": 232, "events": [["submit", 446352]], "time_left_end": "189", "answered_time": 446352, "user_answer": "232", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "189", "question_time_start": 446352, "question": "78+23+47+86", "correct_answer": 234, "events": [["submit", 461970]], "time_left_end": "173", "answered_time": 461970, "user_answer": "234", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "173", "question_time_start": 461971, "question": "57+839", "correct_answer": 896, "events": [["submit", 470402]], "time_left_end": "165", "answered_time": 470402, "user_answer": "896", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "165", "question_time_start": 470402, "question": "8+47+49", "correct_answer": 104, "events": [["submit", 476548]], "time_left_end": "159", "answered_time": 476548, "user_answer": "104", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "159", "question_time_start": 476548, "question": "18+528", "correct_answer": 546, "events": [["submit", 484955]], "time_left_end": "150", "answered_time": 484955, "user_answer": "546", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "150", "question_time_start": 484957, "question": "4+3+4+88", "correct_answer": 99, "events": [["submit", 489678]], "time_left_end": "146", "answered_time": 489678, "user_answer": "99", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "146", "question_time_start": 489679, "question": "46+258", "correct_answer": 304, "events": [["submit", 498269]], "time_left_end": "137", "answered_time": 498269, "user_answer": "304", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "137", "question_time_start": 498270, "question": "9+6+6+24", "correct_answer": 45, "events": [["submit", 502300]], "time_left_end": "133", "answered_time": 502300, "user_answer": "45", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 9, "start_time": 502300, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "133", "question_time_start": 502300, "question": "67+96+13+67", "correct_answer": 243, "events": [["submit", 515072]], "time_left_end": "120", "answered_time": 515072, "user_answer": "143", "user_correct": "False", "score": "13"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "120", "question_time_start": 515073, "question": "69+163", "correct_answer": 232, "events": [["submit", 524075]], "time_left_end": "111", "answered_time": 524075, "user_answer": "238", "user_correct": "False", "score": "12"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "111", "question_time_start": 524075, "question": "7+19+83", "correct_answer": 109, "events": [["submit", 528260]], "time_left_end": "107", "answered_time": 528260, "user_answer": "109", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "107", "question_time_start": 528261, "question": "7+89+64", "correct_answer": 160, "events": [["submit", 536067]], "time_left_end": "99", "answered_time": 536067, "user_answer": "169", "user_correct": "False", "score": "12"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "99", "question_time_start": 536067, "question": "56+494", "correct_answer": 550, "events": [["submit", 541265]], "time_left_end": "94", "answered_time": 541265, "user_answer": "550", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "94", "question_time_start": 541265, "question": "84+43+26+49", "correct_answer": 202, "events": [["submit", 555428]], "time_left_end": "80", "answered_time": 555428, "user_answer": "201", "user_correct": "False", "score": "12"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "80", "question_time_start": 555428, "question": "44+579", "correct_answer": 623, "events": [["submit", 564556]], "time_left_end": "71", "answered_time": 564556, "user_answer": "621", "user_correct": "False", "score": "11"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "71", "question_time_start": 564557, "question": "94+96+834", "correct_answer": 1024, "events": [["submit", 576470]], "time_left_end": "59", "answered_time": 576470, "user_answer": "1024", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "59", "question_time_start": 576471, "question": "6+8+9+98", "correct_answer": 121, "events": [["submit", 586400]], "time_left_end": "49", "answered_time": 586400, "user_answer": "121", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "49", "question_time_start": 586402, "question": "7+7+3+28", "correct_answer": 45, "events": [["submit", 592227]], "time_left_end": "43", "answered_time": 592226, "user_answer": "45", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 9, "start_time": 592227, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "43", "question_time_start": 592227, "question": "64+88+53+74", "correct_answer": 279, "events": [["submit", 609952]], "time_left_end": "25", "answered_time": 609952, "user_answer": "279", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "25", "question_time_start": 609953, "question": "4+13+73", "correct_answer": 90, "events": [["submit", 617098]], "time_left_end": "18", "answered_time": 617098, "user_answer": "100", "user_correct": "False", "score": "14"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "18", "question_time_start": 617099, "question": "9+6+4+64", "correct_answer": 83, "events": [["submit", 623187]], "time_left_end": "12", "answered_time": 623187, "user_answer": "83", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "12", "question_time_start": 623188, "question": "34+26+97+39", "correct_answer": 196, "events": [["submit", 630382]], "time_left_end": "5", "answered_time": 630382, "user_answer": "196", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "5", "question_time_start": 630382, "question": "48+947", "correct_answer": 995, "events": []}}}}}